{"sents": {"0": [{"sent": "The man the dinner burned.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "WO*", "num": "1", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Many house were destroyed by the flood.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PL*", "num": "2", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "The boy is speak to a policeman.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PP*", "num": "3", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Janie slept with her dolls last night.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PT", "num": "4", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Mary opens the windows in her room.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "DET", "num": "5", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Is waiting Sally in the car?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "AUX*", "num": "6", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "John's dog always waits for him outside.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "3PS", "num": "7", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "The boy feeds the rabbits carrots.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "WO", "num": "8", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Is being Lucy held by his mother?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "AUX*", "num": "9", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "A bat flew into our attic yesterday.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PT", "num": "10", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Three boys played on the swings.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PL", "num": "11", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "John sang for the church choir yesterday.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PT", "num": "12", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Drinks the young man.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "WO*", "num": "13", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "We are teaching herself the Spanish alphabet.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PRO*", "num": "14", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "I want you will go to school.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "SUB*", "num": "15", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Roy will be leaving the party early.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "AUX", "num": "16", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "The boy put the book in the kitchen", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "SUB", "num": "17", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Right this minute the ship is sinking.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "IC", "num": "18", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Janet is wear the dress right now.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PP*", "num": "19", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "The girls enjoy singing Karaoke.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "SUB", "num": "20", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Tom walked the hall down to Stephanie.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PM*", "num": "21", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Yesterday the woman satted on her porch.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PT*", "num": "22", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Alex brought corns to the company picnic.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PL*", "num": "23", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "She stepped in the room carefully.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PM", "num": "24", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Many men came to the club.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PL", "num": "25", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Grace cooks eggs for Jerry last night.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "IC*", "num": "26", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Can the boy can drive a tractor?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "AUX*", "num": "27", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "The policeman was talking to a woman.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "SUB", "num": "28", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Where did she put the book?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "WHSUB", "num": "29", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Ryan lives with Max every summer.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "IC", "num": "30", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Danced Bill at the party yesterday?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "AUX*", "num": "31", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "They took their children to the theater.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PRO", "num": "32", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "John should have given food to Cindy.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "AUX", "num": "33", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Where did Arnie hunted last year?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "TENSE*", "num": "34", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "What the boy will read next?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "WH*", "num": "35", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "He is fixing the bicycle tire.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PRO", "num": "36", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Fred will be get a raise tomorrow.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "AUX*", "num": "37", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "The horse jumped over the fence yesterday.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PM", "num": "38", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Where do you work during the summer?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "WH", "num": "39", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Leonard should has written to Katrina.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "AUX*", "num": "40", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Tammy bought rice at the grocery store.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PL", "num": "41", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Who you meet every day?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "WH*", "num": "42", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Two mouses ran into the house.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PL*", "num": "43", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Susan is making some cookies for us.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PRO", "num": "44", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "The cat is hiding underneath the couch.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "AUX", "num": "45", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Arnold may have be sleeping.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "AUX*", "num": "46", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "I hope you will go to Canada.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "SUB", "num": "47", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Tom drove himselve's sister to the concert.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PRO*", "num": "48", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Does Jane learn math from Mr. Thompson?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "AUX", "num": "49", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Yesterday the hunter shot a deer.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "IC", "num": "50", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "At this moment Judy shops.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "IC*", "num": "51", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Why did the company send?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "WHSUB*", "num": "52", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "The glass broke into pieces.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PM", "num": "53", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Has the king been served his dinner?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "AUX", "num": "54", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "We ate the whole pizza by ourselves.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PRO", "num": "55", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Will Larry feed the cat tomorrow?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "AUX", "num": "56", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Linda a cake baked John.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "WO*", "num": "57", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Yesterday the books falled off the shelves.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PT*", "num": "58", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Can the little girl ride a bicycle?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "AUX", "num": "59", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Larry went the home after the party.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "DET*", "num": "60", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Tom is reading a book upstairs.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "DET", "num": "61", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "What is Martha bringing to the party?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "WH", "num": "62", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Terri frequently Talk with Martha.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "3PS*", "num": "63", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "What does Janet pay her gardener?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "WH", "num": "64", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "The tall woman paints.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "WO", "num": "65", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Yesterday the man make a chocolate cake.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PT*", "num": "66", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "The little boys laughed the clown.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "SUB*", "num": "67", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "The girl likes the movie.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "WO", "num": "68", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Paul often is meeting George at school.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "IC*", "num": "69", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Will wear Harry his tie to work?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "AUX*", "num": "70", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Every Friday our neighbor washes her car.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "TPS", "num": "71", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "The kids would have eaten by now.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "AUX", "num": "72", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Bites the scary dog.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "WO*", "num": "73", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Can George hear us from there?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "AUX", "num": "74", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "When will Sam fix his car?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "WH", "num": "75", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Yesterday the baby throwed a cat.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PT*", "num": "76", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Right now Bart watched a game.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "IC*", "num": "77", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Who did the teacher smile?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "WHSUB*", "num": "78", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Right now Kate is dreaming about Greg.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "IC", "num": "79", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Mrs. Johnson went to library yesterday.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "DET*", "num": "80", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "The ball the boy caught.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "WO*", "num": "81", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "The farmers were hoping for rain.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "SUB", "num": "82", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Does Martha use her microwave oven?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "WH", "num": "83", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Sandy filled the jar with cookies yesterday.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PT", "num": "84", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Todd has many coats in his closet.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PL", "num": "85", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "A boys are going to the zoo.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PET*", "num": "86", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Andrew is helping Judy build a house.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "DET", "num": "87", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "The man climbed up the ladder carefully.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PM", "num": "88", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "George says his prayers much too softly.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "SUB", "num": "89", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "A shoe salesman always sees many foots.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PL*", "num": "90", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "What do they sell at the store?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "WH", "num": "91", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "The dog is barking at the mailman.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PP", "num": "92", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "A snake bit she one the leg.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PRO*", "num": "93", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Will Harry be blamed for the accident?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "AUX", "num": "94", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "They stood the line in very patiently.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PM*", "num": "95", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Santa hid his money yesterday.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PT", "num": "96", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Sheeps graze in the field.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PL*", "num": "97", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Yesterday Sam is standing in the rain.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "IC*", "num": "98", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Did Janet swim in the race yesterday?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "AUX", "num": "99", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Carol is cooking dinner for hers family.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PRO*", "num": "100", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "The man allows his son watch TV.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "SUB*", "num": "101", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "The bird has fall from the tree.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "AUX*", "num": "102", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "You must have skipped lunch", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "AUX", "num": "103", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Mrs. Sampson clean her house every Wednesday.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "TPS*", "num": "104", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Kevin called Amy for a date up.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PM*", "num": "105", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Anna lost two teeth in the fight.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PL", "num": "106", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Christina cut himself.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PRO*", "num": "107", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Yesterday the teacher sented a letter.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PT*", "num": "108", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Knows John the answers?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "AUX*", "num": "109", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Jeff has been lie to his father.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "AUX*", "num": "110", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Where Ted is working this summer?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "WH*", "num": "111", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "A tourist a question asked grandpa.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "WO*", "num": "112", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Should have Timothy gone to the party?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "AUX*", "num": "113", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Why did the man go?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "WHSUB", "num": "114", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "George has been cleaning for hours.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "AUX", "num": "115", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Girl played with her friend outside.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "DET*", "num": "116", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "The woman is holding her newborn baby.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PP", "num": "117", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "The man lets his son watch TV.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "SUB", "num": "118", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Have you seen Jane's new baby?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "AUX", "num": "119", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Them worked on the project all night.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PRO*", "num": "120", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Ken counted all his pennies last night.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "IC", "num": "121", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "The farmer bought two pig.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PL*", "num": "122", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "When they leave for Mexico?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "WH*", "num": "123", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "The girl's swimsuit is full of sand.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PL", "num": "124", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Did Bobby stayed at home last night.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "WH*", "num": "125", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Linda poured herself a glass of lemonade.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PRO", "num": "126", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "The girls want watching TV.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "SUB*", "num": "127", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Will the girl can hurt the kitten?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "AUX*", "num": "128", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Yesterday Mrs. Smith die in her sleep.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PT*", "num": "129", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Chris may is moving to Chicago tomorrow.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "AUX*", "num": "130", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "A policeman gave Tom a ticket yesterday.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PT", "num": "131", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "He came my house at six.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "SUB*", "num": "132", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Tim looked the new cars at yesterday.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PM*", "num": "133", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Jenna raced her friend to the fence.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PRO", "num": "134", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "The men played basketball at school.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "DET", "num": "135", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "The man looked the new cars over yesterday.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "A", "gram": "PM", "num": "136", "answer": "n"}], "1": [{"sent": "A tourist asked grandpa a question.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "WO", "num": "1", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "When did the teacher smile?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "WHSUG", "num": "2", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Linda baked John a cake.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "WO", "num": "3", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "The woman is hold her newborn baby.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PP*", "num": "4", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Carol is cooking dinner for her family.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PRO", "num": "5", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Where you work during the summer?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "WH*", "num": "6", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "The man lets his son to watch TV.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "SUG*", "num": "7", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Janet is wearing the dress right now.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PP", "num": "8", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "The cat is hide underneath the couch.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "AUX*", "num": "9", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "The scary dog bites.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "WO", "num": "10", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "When Sam will fix his car?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "WH*", "num": "11", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Roy will is leaving the party early.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "AUX*", "num": "12", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Will Larry will feed the cat tomorrow?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "AUX*", "num": "13", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Many houses were destroyed by the flood.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PL", "num": "14", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Mary opens a windows in her room.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "DEL*", "num": "15", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Santa hidded his money yesterday.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PT*", "num": "16", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Learns Jane math from Mr. Thompson.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "AUX*", "num": "17", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "A snake bit her on the leg.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PRO", "num": "18", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "I want you to go to school.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "SUB", "num": "19", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "The farmer bought two pigs.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PL", "num": "20", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Mrs. Johnson went to the library yesterday.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "DET", "num": "21", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "John should have give food to Cindy.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "AUX*", "num": "22", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Right this minute the ship sinks.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "IC*", "num": "23", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Yesterday Sam stood in the rain.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "IC", "num": "24", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "What does Janet pays her gardener?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "WH*", "num": "25", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Sandy fill the jar with cookies yesterday.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PT*", "num": "26", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "They stood in the line very patiently.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PM", "num": "27", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "The boy caught the ball.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "WO", "num": "28", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "What did the company send?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "WHSUB", "num": "29", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Anna lost two teeths in the fight.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PL*", "num": "30", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "The girls want to watch TV.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "SUB", "num": "31", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Janie sleeped with her dolls last night.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PT*", "num": "32", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "The man climbed the ladder up carefully.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PM*", "num": "33", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Will be Harry blamed for the accident?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "AUX*", "num": "34", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Christina cut herself.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PRO", "num": "35", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Is Sally waiting in the car?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "AUX", "num": "36", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "The girl's swimsuit is full of sands.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PL*", "num": "37", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Every Friday our neighbor wash her car.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "3PS*", "num": "38", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Yesterday the hunter shoots a deer.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "IC*", "num": "39", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Paul often meets George at school.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "IC", "num": "40", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "The horse jumped the fence over yesterday.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PM*", "num": "41", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "The man burned the dinner.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "WO", "num": "42", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "The girls enjoy to sing Karaoke.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "SUB*", "num": "43", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "They worked on the project all night.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PRO", "num": "44", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Larry went home after the party.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "DET", "num": "45", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "George says much too softly.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "SUB*", "num": "46", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Arnold may have been sleeping.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "AUX", "num": "47", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Right now Kate drempt about Greg.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "IC*", "num": "48", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Yesterday Mrs. Smith died in her sleep.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PT", "num": "49", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Is Lucy being held by his mother?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "AUX", "num": "50", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Jenna raced herselves friend to the fence.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PRO*", "num": "51", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Todd has many coat in his closet.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PL*", "num": "52", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Two mice ran into the house.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PL", "num": "53", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Alex brought corn to the company picnic.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PL", "num": "54", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "A bat flewed into our attic yesterday.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PT*", "num": "55", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Yesterday the man made a chocolate cake.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PT", "num": "56", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "The young man drinks.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "WO", "num": "57", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Who do you meet every day?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "WH", "num": "58", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "The kids would has eaten by now.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "AUX*", "num": "59", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "What did the man go?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "WHSUB*", "num": "60", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "The farmers were hoping rain.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "SUB*", "num": "61", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Right now Bart is watching a game.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "IC", "num": "62", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Yesterday the baby threw a cat.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PT", "num": "63", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Tom waked down the hall to Stephanie.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PM", "num": "64", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "You must have skip lunch", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "AUX*", "num": "65", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Does John know the answers?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "AUX", "num": "66", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Linda poured themselves a glass of lemonade.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PRO*", "num": "67", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "What will the boy read next?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "WH", "num": "68", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Have seen you Jane's new baby?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "AUX*", "num": "69", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Can the boy drive a tractor?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "AUX", "num": "70", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "He came to my house at six.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "SUB", "num": "71", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "John's dog always wait for him outside.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "3PS*", "num": "72", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Ryan is living with Max every summer.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "IC*", "num": "73", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Where did Arnie hunt last year?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "WH", "num": "74", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Does Martha uses her microwave oven?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "WH*", "num": "75", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Yesterday the teacher sent a letter.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PT", "num": "76", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Can George will hear us from there?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "AUX*", "num": "77", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Why did she put the book?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "WHSUB*", "num": "78", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Andrew is helping Judy build house.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "DET*", "num": "79", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Three boy played on the swings.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PL*", "num": "80", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Did Bill dance at the party yesterday?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "AUX", "num": "81", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "When do they leave for Mexico?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "WH", "num": "82", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Fred will be getting a raise tomorrow.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "AUX", "num": "83", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Kevin called Amy up for a date.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PM", "num": "84", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "What they sell at the store?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "WH*", "num": "85", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Susan is making some cookies for we.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PRO*", "num": "86", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Will Harry wear his tie to work?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "AUX", "num": "87", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Yesterday the woman sat on her porch.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PT", "num": "88", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "She stepped the room in carefully.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PM*", "num": "89", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "A policemen gived Tom a ticket yesterday.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PT*", "num": "90", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Paints the tall woman.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "WO*", "num": "91", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Has been the king served his dinner?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "AUX*", "num": "92", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Tom drove his sister to the concert.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PRO", "num": "93", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "The boy is speaking to a policeman.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PP", "num": "94", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "We are teaching ourselves the Spanish alphabet.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PRO", "num": "95", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "I hope you to go to Canada.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "SUB*", "num": "96", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Chris may be moving to Chicago tomorrow.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "AUX", "num": "97", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "The men played the basketball at school.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "DET*", "num": "98", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "The girl played with her friend outside.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "DET", "num": "99", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "A shoe salesman always sees many feet.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PL", "num": "100", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "What Martha is bringing to the party?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "WH*", "num": "101", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Tammy bought rices at the grocery store.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PL*", "num": "102", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "The little boys laughed at the clown.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "SUB", "num": "103", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Mrs. Sampson cleans her house every Wednesday.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "3PS", "num": "104", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "George has be cleaning for hours.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "AUX*", "num": "105", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Grace cooked eggs for Jerry last night.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "IC", "num": "106", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Tim looked at the new cars yesterday.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PM", "num": "107", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Yesterday the books fell off the shelves.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PT", "num": "108", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Should Timothy have gone to the party?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "AUX", "num": "109", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "The man allows his son to watch TV.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "SUB", "num": "110", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Swam Janet in the race yesterday.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "AUX*", "num": "111", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "The dog is bark at the mailman.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PP*", "num": "112", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Leonard should have written to Katrina.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "AUX", "num": "113", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Many mens came to the club.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PL*", "num": "114", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Can ride the little girl a bicycle.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "AUX*", "num": "115", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Will the girl hurt the kitten?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "AUX", "num": "116", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "The policeman was talking a woman.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "SUB*", "num": "117", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Terri frequently talks with Martha.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "3PS", "num": "118", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Ken is counting all his pennies last night.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "IC*", "num": "119", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "At this moment Judy is shopping.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "IC", "num": "120", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "John sing for the church choir yesterday.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PT*", "num": "121", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "The glass broke pieces into.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PM*", "num": "122", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Did Bobby stay at home last night?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "WH", "num": "123", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "The bird has fallen from the tree.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "AUX", "num": "124", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Sheep graze in the field.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PL", "num": "125", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Tom is reading book upstairs.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "DET*", "num": "126", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "The boy put the book at the kitchen.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "SUB*", "num": "127", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Where is Ted working this summer?", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "WH", "num": "128", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "Him is fixing the bicycle tire.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PRO*", "num": "129", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "They took theirs children to the theater.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PRO*", "num": "130", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "The man looked the new cars yesterday over.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PM*", "num": "131", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "The boys are going to the zoo.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "DET", "num": "132", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "We ate the whole pizza by themselves.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "PRO*", "num": "133", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "Jeff has been lying to his father.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "AUX", "num": "134", "answer": "n"}, {"sent": "The boy the rabbits feeds carrots.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "WO*", "num": "135", "answer": "y"}, {"sent": "The girl the movie likes.", "question": "Were there any errors in the sentence?", "group": "B", "gram": "WO*", "num": "136", "answer": "y"}]}}